Hello English learners and welcome
to English Pod, my name is Marco.
I'm Amira and Amira and I are here
today with a great, great lesson for you.
Yes, we are.
Today we're going to be
talking about a restaurant.
Amira, why don't you give
us a little bit more details?
Well, we're talking about
a situation in a restaurant
and two people are involved,
the waiter and the customer.
And I don't want to say anymore.
Okay, don't say anymore.
Let's just listen to this dialogue
and we'll be back later to explain it.
Good evening.
My name is Fabio. I'll be your waiter
for tonight. May I take your order?
No, I'm still working on it.
This man is not even in English.
What's good here?
For you, sir, I would recommend
spaghetti and meatballs.
Does it come with Coke and fries?
It comes with either soup or salad
and complimentary glass of wine, sir.
I'll go with the spaghetti and
meatballs, salad and the wine.
Excellent choice.
Your order will be ready soon.
How soon is soon?
20 minutes?
You know what? I'll just go
grab a burger across the street.
Oh, oh, why the waiter?
What a waiter.
He is really angry at this
customer and I can't blame him.
I would be angry too.
Yeah, so I think Marco, you have chosen
some interesting expressions for us here.
What is the first one?
Well, the first one is
I'm still working on it.
Why don't we listen to some
other examples on how you can
use this word and then
we'll come back and explain it.
Did you finish reading the magazine?
I'm still working on it.
Did you fix my cost?
Ah, so you could say
I'm still working on it.
Means?
I still need more time.
Fantastic.
Great. Okay, it's clear.
I have another one for you guys.
It's a phrase commonly used
and you'll hear it all the time.
Coke and fries.
It's a short way of saying
Coca-Cola and French fries.
So that's basically America's fast food.
Yeah, burger, Coke and fries.
Okay.
What's next on the menu?
On the menu we have a
complimentary glass of wine.
Complimentary glass of wine.
Complimentary means that it's free.
Yes.
We love that, huh?
Yeah, we definitely like free things.
Well, I have another one for us here.
Another interesting phrase, I'll go with.
I'll go with.
So basically it's another
way of saying I'm choosing.
Yeah, I'll choose or I'll take.
I'll take.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, very good.
All right.
The next word that I want
to take a look at is grab.
Grab.
Okay.
Now let's listen to
some other examples of
how we could use grab
in different situations.
And then we'll come back and explain it.
Let's grab some milk.
Wait for me, please.
I need to grab my coat.
Let's grab a cup of coffee.
All right.
Well, I would understand that
go grab means go get quickly.
To go get quickly, yeah.
Yeah.
All right, everyone.
So now it's time to listen one more
time to the dialogue and listen carefully.
And try to understand why the
waiter doesn't like the customer.
Let's listen.
Good evening.
My name is Fabio.
I'll be your waiter for tonight.
May I take your order?
No, I'm still working on it.
This man is not even in English.
What's good here?
For you, sir, I would recommend
spaghetti and meatballs.
Does it come with Coke and fries?
It comes with either soup or salad
and complimentary glass of wine, sir.
I'll go with the spaghetti and
meatballs, salad and the wine.
Excellent choice.
Your order will be ready soon.
How soon is soon?
20 minutes?
You know what?
I'll just go grab a
burger across the street.
Marco, why did this waiter
get angry at the customer?
Well, he basically
wasted the waiter's time.
I mean, this guy comes into the restaurant.
He is not very polite.
And he's asking all of these questions.
And he just gets up and says, "I'll
just go grab a burger across the street.
" Yeah, and I also think
that this guy was a lot
more casual than the
place he was in, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I think this was a nice fancy restaurant,
so I think he was in the wrong place.
Yeah.
So how many times, Marco, tell me,
do you really have fast food a week?
Fast food.
Let's see.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday.
Oh, my God.
No, no.
I think I get fast food maybe
once a week, once or twice a week.
All right.
Talking about fast food made me hungry.
So I think I'm going to go
grab something to eat myself.
Yeah, me too.
All right.
I hope you guys enjoyed the lesson today.
And remember that all of this vocabulary
is useful for your everyday needs.
Yes.
Well, actually here in
English pod, we focus
on phrases and words
that are high frequency.
And that means that you can use
them every day in your practical life.
Exactly.
And be sure to go to
our website at EnglishPod.
com, where you can
find many other resources,
and you can leave your questions
and comments at our community forum.
So thank you very much for listening.
We'll be back tomorrow with
another great lesson for you.
So until then, bye.
Bye.
[MUSIC PLAYING]